sellics.com 2017-11-20

# Privacy Policy | Sellics

## Sellics Company Information & Privacy Policy

**Your privacy is important to us!**

This privacy policy outlines the types of information we collect when you use the service offered by Sellics, how we use this information as well as some of the steps we take to protect it.

**Which personal information do we collect?**  
When using our service, you may be asked to enter your name, email, address, credit card information and other details. Personal information may be collected when users visit our site, register on the site, place an order or during other activities.

**Which non-personal identification information do we collect?**  
We may collect non-personally identifying information your browser makes available whenever you visit a website. This information includes your Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your query and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.

**How do we use personal information?**  
Sellics may collect and use personal information for the following purposes:  
to manage this website  
to personalize the website for users  
to enable your access to and use of the website services  
to send to you statements and invoices  
to collect payments from you  
to send you marketing communications

**How do we protect your information?**  
We will take appropriate technical and organizational precautions to prevent the loss, abuse or manipulation of your personal information.  
We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, manipulation, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our site.

We do not sell, trade, or rent users’ personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

**Transfers of data across borders**  
Collected information may be stored and used in and transferred between any of the countries in which we operate to enable the use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy.  
By using our service, the user agrees to such cross-border transfers of personal information.

**To be in accordance with CANSPAM, we agree to the following:**  
NOT to use false, or misleading subjects or email addresses  
Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way  
Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters  
Monitor third party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.  
Approve opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly  
Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email

**Changes to this privacy policy**  
Jordan, Vataman & Dr. Thiel GbR may update this privay policy from time to time. Any changes will be posted on www.sellics.com We advise you to check this page periodically for any changes.

**Contacting us**  
If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

www.Sellics.com  
Jordan & Dr. Thiel GbR  
Baerwarldstr.14  
Berlin 10961  
Germany  
support@sellics.com

**Disclaimer**  
Sellics, nor its operators, are affiliated with or funded by Amazon.com, Inc. in any way.
